Previously on Love Island All-Stars...
There were departures...
Jo and Joanna.
And a new arrival made his move.
The girl that I would like to steal is Arabella.
Chris, you are now single and have therefore been dumped from the villa.
Please pack your bags and say goodbyes.
Tonight, one boy's having doubts.
I just don't feel like I found that spark.
Casey is basically now saying he doesn't know if him and Eve could work in the outside.
What?
And the power is in your hands.
Islanders, the public have been voting for their favourite couple.
The couples with the fewest votes are at risk of being dumped
from the island tonight.
Tonight.
Bombshell Adam is in the villa.
I wanted to ask him how he got his wrestling nickname, Flex,
but he was too busy biting his toenails.
Now, Adam's stolen Arabella, meaning Chris has been dumped.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
I haven't seen eye to eye, but, honestly, you're amazing.
Thank you.
Hey, Mum.
I feel like I've taken one of the biggest energies
from the villa, though, do you know what I mean?
I breathe slow, let go, then give it to the water.
Give it to the war, darlin'
I'll see you in a minute.
He's going to be missed by us all, for sure.
Top bloke, and I can't wait to see him on the outside, to be honest.
Sad boys.
Thanks for being here with me, though.
Oh, man.
Chris has been there from day dot with me,
like, always been someone I could talk to.
You're going to be a miss, brother.
Thanks, mate.
It's been an absolute ride, boys.
Ups and downs, highs and lows.
I've enjoyed every waking second with you all.
I love you all, deeply.
See you on the outside.
See you later, Chris.
See you, guys.
Thank you, guys.
Hello, Chris.
Hello, babe.
How are you doing?
Oh, I'm furious.
You're fuming?
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah, look at my face.
I'm furious.
Do you look happy?
I'm quite happy.
Yeah?
How was that experience?
Did you expect to get dumped like that?
Actually, no.
I didn't expect it.
Your fellow Islanders, they did look really sad to see you leave, especially Georgia and
Toby.
Yeah, they had a little cry.
You obviously got quite close with those guys in there.
Yeah, I was really close, really close with Toby from the beginning, really.
And G's always been like my little sister anyway.
I knew her before.
Like, we've always had that vibe.
Well, let's talk about your journey now, Chris, because you coupled up with Arabella.
And you know, at one point, it looked like you could be a perfect match.
You had a date together on the rowing boat, everything was all lovey-lovey, and then...
I'd literally been so vulnerable with her on the date,
and then I just felt like it had been thrown straight back in my face later that night.
And Joanna came in.
I would say swooped you off your feet, but it wasn't that smooth, was it?
Joanna walked in.
I fancied Joanna for a good while.
How long did you fancy Joanna for beforehand?
A good four years.
What?
So, yeah, when she walked in, I was quite excited.
It was quite weird in, like, the group scenario at the beginning.
Like, she was talking to everyone, but only really looking at me.
Like, the eye contact was pretty mad.
But then, obviously, the game happened.
It got left at a really awkward point,
when we were, like, smack bang in the middle of figuring it out
and what it could have been and all that kind of stuff.
So, like, yeah, left with questions.
And now your Love Island journey's over.
Do you hope to make things work with Joanna on the outside now?
Well, we definitely need a conversation.
Cos I really enjoy getting to know her.
We were quite early on, but the amount of people in there
that were saying, like, you two are, like, the same person,
like, you've got the same energy.
Unfortunately, they're the same people
that voted as most incompatible.
Right.
Which is quite hilarious when you think about it.
But, yeah, I'm definitely gonna have a chat.
Yeah, where there's love, there's hope
in all those things they say, isn't there?
Chris, it has been an absolute pleasure watching you.
All the way from the beginning, you've made us laugh,
and I feel like we've definitely got to know you
a bit better this time.
Yeah.
Yeah, all right, well, thank you so much.
Look after yourself.
Thank you.
Ooh, you smell delicious.
Back in the villa, Toby and Georgia S are finding Chris's departure tough to take.
He's the other one that booted for us, do you know what I mean?
No.
We got each other.
Yeah.
Do you want me to come over or not?
Yeah, come over as well.
Get me.
I'm glad you're behind us.
You can go and chat to Joanna, innit?
I feel like that's the...
I feel like that's, like, a comforting...
I think that's something that could continue in the outside world.
I feel like I'm in shock.
It's another one where, like, you're fighting back the tears.
It's just so hard.
Arabella's fallen for wrestler Adam.
Be careful, mate.
Normally, when that happens,
Adam pins you to the floor and counts to three.
Adam...
Where is it?
I feel like you'd get more of a serious, deeper side as well.
Like, you'll be able to talk to him.
Sexy, yeah.
He wrestles as well.
So sexy.
He seems like a good lad, though.
He seems really...
She's smitten already.
She's like a cat with nine lives.
She just keeps coming back!
You know he's a wrestler?
He can wrestle me around!
LAUGHTER
Any day.
Let's go talk about it.
LAUGHTER
Oh!
Yeah, smooth.
That was...
That was a smooth transition, that.
LAUGHTER
Honestly, this is the happiest I've been and felt
since the second I walked in this villa.
I feel like my journey in here now makes sense.
I'm happy you picked me.
I was going to ask you about that.
Yeah, I'm very, very happy.
I'm not going to lie, I was hoping when you walked in,
I was like, hmm, I hope he picks me.
Was the speech all right?
It was, it was.
I feel like you like hit the nail on the head.
I think you're just like a really flirty person.
Oh, I am?
I think you just flirt with everyone.
No, I don't flirt.
Maybe you don't even realise you are.
Is this how you are?
You just have good energy?
Yeah.
I'm a flirty person, but I think if I'm into someone there's certain ways I do respect
You've got to have boundaries as well
Oh, 100%
Because I'm like, like I said, I'm at a stage now where I'm ready to meet someone and actually
have something serious
Yeah
I've made mistakes before and now I know what I want to, I mean, but
I think life is about making mistakes, I think, like, I've made a lot of mistakes in my life
and I feel like if you don't make mistakes, like, you don't have anything to go by of
like what's right, what's wrong
Every mistake is a lesson
Yeah, exactly
Like, what is, like, a good, like, first date?
What would you, like...
Are you a dinner person and drinks?
No, it depends, obviously, where we are.
On a...
Well, where we are or where the person and me is.
Is this a date?
It could be a date.
I give this cheers to first date.
First date.
You have to look into my eyes.
Oh, you get seven years bad sex?
Look into my eye.
I'll never have seven years.
You can't get bad sex with me.
Wow, we're on the same...
I feel like you've damned me in here for a reason, for sure.
This is kind of going too well.
I know, I'm slightly scared.
I haven't been in a situation like that in a while now,
where I've got a very attractive woman in front of me
and I'm chatting to them, and it just felt effortless.
Like, the conversation flowed, there was no awkward silences.
I just feel like the more we have these conversations,
we'll learn more and more about each other.
Yeah, I'm excited about that, jeez.
So, Chris is gone.
I enjoyed Maya's interview earlier,
although she did forget the million dollar question.
I mean, what is Chris's favourite farmyard animal?
Right, all-stars, off to bed.
Happier than you were with Joe?
Very.
Really?
You excited, Arabella?
SHE LAUGHS
Oh, the best day, and a bittersweet night.
Night!
Night guys
Someday I want a love like the love I had with you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh.
It's morning and wrestler Adam suddenly realised that the last time he was
surrounded by 11 people flat on their backs,
he just won the All-Ireland Battle Royale Championships.
MUSIC
Morning, everyone.
Morning, Robert.
How was your first sleep in bed with Arabella?
We had a nice cuddle.
Did you?
Yeah, it was nice.
It is weird without Chris's voice in the morning, isn't it?
These two were locking lips, and all I had was like this.
Yeah, a kissing corner over there.
Coffee time, then.
I feel small in his arms.
How is that possible?
A nice surprise in addition, for sure.
Do you put milk in?
Yeah.
You have to with Eggy Rose.
Did you kiss him?
No.
I never knew you kissed Joe.
Now Bella does not waste any time.
Time is of the essence, guys.
Psych scoffer.
Don't give it to Jack.
The kissy-wissy.
SHE SCREAMS
Shut up!
No, he didn't.
You've literally been kissing all night.
Oh, I'm going to cry!
She's loving it!
SHE LAUGHS
It was Dave wasn't even thinking, just going like,
I'd give him a copy, give it straight to Eve.
LAUGHTER
At least I know now to give it to the one that hasn't got one.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's not going to live that down.
Giving the wrong coffees, are we?
Yeah!
Oh, you big man.
Do you know what, I actually feel, like, real good, do you know what I mean?
I have to come in this time and, as a bombshell, do what I need to do
and do like what's for my journey.
I think I need to chat to people
because like even just the energy you bring to the villa,
like if you shut yourself off from people,
you're not getting the full experience.
I think I'll definitely obviously grab people
and just chill and just see what the vibe is
and just get to know people.
Yeah, absolutely bro.
And I don't think you're doing anything wrong at that
by doing that as well.
Oh, I feel awkward.
You're like a little kid.
Oh God.
Go on then, let's start with you then.
Yeah, come on.
You okay?
Well, I feel like everything now makes sense.
I feel like, like...
LAUGHTER
It's taken four weeks.
Shut up.
Come on.
But I feel like, obviously, in here, I do feel like I've had, like, a mad journey, and
I feel like everyone that I've been coupled up with has not felt as, like, right as this.
Yeah.
And I feel like it's, like...
Got instincts, telling you.
Yeah.
I was last night with him.
I heard he's in the kissing corner.
I know.
I mean...
Smoochy, smoochy.
I feel like that was Anton and George.
I heard you in Kiss and Call the last time.
Yeah, I was going to say, Jesus Christ, literally all I heard...
******* I heard it, just eating each other's face.
Jesus Christ, have things stepped up a notch, then?
We get on like an awesome five and talk to her for ages, so...
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
It's, erm...
Yeah, it's nice, actually.
I'm happy.
Yeah, good.
Are you interested in getting to know Adam?
I mean, like...
Obviously, I'm not, like, closed off, cos that would be weird,
like, after, like, a year and a half.
like, after, like, this long, I don't think, um...
Like, initially, I don't think I would be, like,
I really want to get to know him, but I'm still open.
Do you think anyone else in here would be as tight?
You never know.
Only time's going to tell, really, innit?
I feel like today he's probably going to have a chat
with a few of the girls, for sure.
He's a bombshell.
He has no allowance to anybody.
If you want to chat to more than one girl,
you're fully entitled to do it.
Grab the ball by the horns.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly, exactly.
For sure.
Chris is gone, but he promised that when he got out, he'd give Toby a ring.
You could have given her a ring before you left, Chris.
Your bloody fingers were covered in them.
Jay, how do you think Toby's feeling today?
I mean, I definitely think he's a bit down, like, it's a bit rubbish.
He's lost his best friend in here.
I'll help you cheer him up if you want.
Yeah.
I think I might go and do him bagels.
What, should we get a little bit cheffy?
Shall we?
What, should the G's get cheffy?
Can I make Anton one as well?
Yeah.
So obviously, Chris has just left the villa.
That was Toby's best friend.
And last night, Toby really, really took it hard.
So we have decided that we are going to make
our men a special breakfast.
Look at me and you cheffing up, G.
I know.
We're like housewives.
Where's the pepper?
Oh, there.
Tobe definitely needs support at the moment.
And if anyone's going to give it to me, it'll be Anton,
cos he's just such an understanding, caring little egg.
And I love an egg.
What we should do is I'll do a plate of bagels,
a plate of avocado.
Yeah.
Plate of egg.
Oh, you're thinking presentation.
And then they can pick what they want from it.
Yeah.
Ready?
I think that's banging, that G.
I'm happy with that.
Yeah.
Shall we call them over?
Yeah, it's getting cold.
It's getting cold.
Boys!
Anton and Tobe.
Anton, what's his name again?
Yeah.
Georgia squared breakfast, can't believe it.
What is going on here?
Are they okay?
No way.
You guys have lost the plot.
Hi, guys.
What's going on?
We just fall since Chris has left the villa.
Yeah.
And obviously, Toby, you lost your best friend.
It would be nice if we could all bond as a family.
Yeah, I think it would be really nice.
Should we let the boys sit next to each other?
Should I go around there?
Yeah, we're one in a life now, bro.
Yeah, we're winning.
We're winning.
This is our first official double date, basically.
Oh my gosh.
We've put, this food wasn't just made normally.
It was made with love.
I don't even want to eat it because it looks so good.
I know.
Oh, shut up.
It looks so good, I don't want to eat it.
Darling.
Oh, I don't know what to say.
Thank you so much, guys.
I don't know what to say.
It's all paid off.
So we say cheers to being happy in our couples,
falling for one another, and friendship.
Yes.
Chin chin.
Chin, guys.
I love yous.
I love yous all.
Jess, I'm grabbing you for it.
Wow, we really are matching.
I'm gonna speak to you as well, though.
What's going on?
Oh, life is good.
How long have you been in here now?
Last night was my fifth night, I think.
And how are you finding everything?
Coming in as a bombshell, it's difficult.
It is hard because everyone is very coupled.
So I'm coupled up with Callum at the moment,
and I'm really happy with how things are going,
but we are still in quite an early stage still.
I mean, you two were kissing and **** so.
Yeah, yeah.
At least you're on that level.
It's obviously moving in the right direction.
I mean, I'm right beside her.
I was like, first night trying to sleep, okay.
No, but it's, no, it's obviously,
It's moving in the right direction, which is good.
How do you feel about that?
You never know.
I don't know where Jess is at.
Have you not had a little chat with her about anything?
No, it's going well.
I know I feel like it's going well anyway.
She thinks it's going well.
Well, it looks like it's going well,
but obviously there's a fresh ******* kid on the block.
I know, mate.
Can't catch a break, can I?
You can't catch a break, can you?
And he's ******* tough, isn't he?
You came in with bombshell energy.
To be transparent, I picked Arabella
because I feel like her energy is good.
and we had a good chat last night,
but probably my mistake, I haven't said to her yet,
that I want to grab other people.
It's been early, so obviously it'd be weird for me
to be like I am in a closed-off couple.
But yeah, we'll just see how it goes.
Casey's been with Eve for three days now.
Well, technically two days.
One day, Eve was a bit under the weather,
so she got Jess to stand in for her.
All right, Shannon.
Come on.
You don't mush.
You both all right?
I'm good, man.
How are you?
Good.
I'm all right.
I think you're just all right, aren't you?
Yeah, I just think it's been, what, now three, four days with Eve,
and, like, we have really been getting along,
and I think she's class,
and I genuinely don't have a bad word to say about her.
Yeah.
And if I'm being real with myself,
I don't think it is going maybe where I want it to go.
I just don't feel like I've found that spark.
It's tough to say, cos I guess I've just got to be real.
It takes a big man to do it, if he's just close.
I've just got to be real, and I don't want to get to the end of here
and end up in the outside with Eve and Lieder on.
And hurting her feelings.
I feel like there's something missing, maybe.
You should be honest with yourself, though.
I don't think it's been easy for anyone, has it?
Apart from Tom and Molly.
Cruising me!
I know, I'm jealous of Tom, I am.
I'm proper buzzing for you, but...
It would be so nice to actually have that experience
where you just absolutely fall for someone in here.
And I don't feel like I've had that
since I first came in the first time round.
If you are thinking about turning, don't leave it too long.
No, I wouldn't do that, cos...
..the more feelings they have, the harder it's going to get.
Yeah.
The journey for a girlfriend continues.
One day, mate.
One day.
Adam's chatting to Eve.
Now, I was talking to Eve earlier.
She asked me if I was from Norway or Cameroon.
Where are you, Scotland or Ireland?
Scotland.
That's an insult.
I'm sure of it.
No, Ireland, Ireland.
Well, fast.
Oh, do you know what?
It's actually very similar, to be fair.
Oh, he's took your girl.
Oh, they're kissing.
Oh, my God, he just smacked her ****.
Wow, she just told him she loves him.
Oh, that's so sweet of her.
You've got a good hearing.
Obviously, it's still early days for me and Casey.
I'm happy with him, I like him, but it's definitely too soon
to close things off and be like, you know,
we're not going to get to know other people.
I think people would look at me and go,
gym guy, like tattoos, maybe you are the *******.
Yeah.
Have you cheated on...?
Oh, After.
I know, I'm like...
Do you know what?
I'm really disappointed in myself.
Do you know what, I think when a guy cheats,
it is a lack of discipline.
lack of discipline.
Lack of discipline.
You're so switched on.
Yeah I feel like I'm really
emotionally intelligent that's just through the mistakes that I've made I'm
like trying to be better and take accountability and like grow up and be a
man and yeah I'm proud of like how I carry myself and hold myself but you
know I just I think I definitely get that stereotype and then people get to
know me they like oh you're actually more than what you yeah like like I'm
sure you as twins as well maybe get that like people judge you and think oh
Yeah, I've got everyone.
Oh, thank you, you've got a good body.
Well, it's all right.
Gym bod.
Yours is better than mine, but...
Oh!
I've got * ****!
Islanders, it's time to serve major looks,
As tonight, you'll be having a pre-loved pink party.
Hashtag pink to make everyone wink, hashtag eBay.
Look at all my friends!
What's up, what's up?
I'm actually so excited.
Pink party.
It's giving Barbie vibes.
Pink to make the boys wink, pink to make the boys...
Pink to make the boys wink, pink, pink, pink.
People say pink is my colour.
So, tonight, I will be busting out the look.
CHEERING
Shall we go and have a look at what we can wear?
Girls, shall we go and have a look?
Bye, Sam.
It's time for the all-stars pink party,
We were going to have a red party and a white party,
but someone mixed the clothes up in the hot wash.
Who's excited?
Yay!
Woo-hoo!
Either way, that power looks so good on you.
How's your first day been?
First day's been good.
Had some good chats.
First night, I'm like, I feel complete now, girls.
******* hell, you feel complete?
He got in here yesterday.
Ah!
Oh, yeah.
Beautiful from head to toe.
I'm ready to go.
You know, you know.
It's pink.
Welcome, Adam, to the villa.
Thank you, guys.
We're so excited to have you.
Can't wait for tonight.
Good vibes.
And looking pretty and pink.
Yay!
I texted a load of my mates and invited them to my pink party.
They all showed up in safety pins and ******* trousers.
Stupid autocorrect.
What are you staring at?
She strikes again.
You look banging tonight.
Thank you.
Very sexy.
Do you like the pink?
I do.
Come on then, talk to me.
I'm talking to you.
I'm just chillin'.
Might have brought you up here for a reason.
Oh, really?
Do you know the tariffs of the...
It seems like a lot of, like, stuff going on up here.
I feel like we had a good day today, though, as well.
Yeah, I feel like it was a nice first day.
I just wanted to give you some space.
Also, I wanted to give you time to, like, chat to other people, as well.
I feel like that was what you needed to do.
But I think, like, I just gravitate back towards, like,
Wanting to spend time with you and talking to you.
It's just effortless, again.
Yeah, it does feel very effortless, for sure.
Just your eyes?
Three biggest turn-ons, what would they be?
Confidence, but not arrogance.
There's a fine line.
Tick.
You're very confident.
Someone that's emotionally intelligent.
It can come with age, but not always.
It's getting hot up here.
Emotionally intelligent.
And what's my third one?
She must.
Hey.
She's got him.
She has got him.
Well, that was my best terrace kiss, I can give you that.
You reckon?
Yeah.
Just see how cheeky, Faye.
Isn't it cheeky?
I didn't think my smile could get bigger, but clearly it can.
You're doing amazing, sweetie!
This is the most pink I've seen on display at a party
since my mate Scotty fell asleep in the sun
at East Agda in Fort of Ventura.
Take a seat, take a seat.
Oh, yes.
How's life treating you?
Life's treating me good, can't complain.
You seem happy.
Very happy.
Very happy I am indeed.
Life's good.
You're close to Josh, what does he say to you?
He doesn't say much, he actually doesn't say that much.
Does he actually not?
Yeah, he does like you though.
You've tamed him.
I've tamed him?
You've tamed him, I think you have anyway.
I feel like he's wild still, but...
How are you doing with my best friend?
Yeah, I'm very happy.
I mean, obviously, you're closest to them both, aren't you?
Yeah.
So how are they both feeling with the situations?
No, she's, um...
Happy?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
It's funny how things work out, isn't it?
Yeah, it is crazy.
Yeah.
How do you think Eve feels about Keita, any...
Why, has he been stressing?
Maybe a little bit.
Why?
I don't, I like, I think, I don't know.
I think you should just check in just to see if Eve,
in case you're on the same page, I'd say.
Oh, is Casey not on the same page?
I think, I don't know.
I think he does like her, and he did say he likes her,
but I don't know.
I don't know.
He's just maybe a bit confused, maybe.
But, I mean.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
You can't, let's start from the beginning.
So, what's Casey said to you?
He's, no, he's, so, he does, he does like Eve.
He does like her.
He's just wondering if, like, that could be a real thing.
I don't know, maybe something on the outside,
like real world stuff.
But I feel like he's gonna talk,
he'll think he's gonna speak to her anyway
and have a conversation with her,
but I'm just relaying to you as a friend,
just in case, like, you might,
because I didn't understand,
I don't know where he was at, like, I don't,
that would just-
Obviously, I need to speak to her first
if she's prepared.
Yeah, but, like, I feel like he will, um,
Casey told me today that his feelings towards Eve,
and maybe just, the spark hasn't come yet,
then fair enough.
And I know Casey wanted to speak to Eve.
I just told Sophie just to make sure,
just to look out for Eve
and make sure she's on the same page as Casey.
Sophie's pulled Eve for a chat
to tell her the news about Casey.
She's invited Jess along too,
just to make doubly sure she's talking to the right twin.
Just been informed something.
Which is just weird.
Bit of weird information.
Go on.
Basically, obviously, you know that I pressed the cowl in here.
Yeah.
He said that he was talking to Kasey.
And Kasey is basically, like, now saying, like,
he doesn't know if him and Eve could work in the outside.
What?
To me, he literally feels completely different.
I know.
And even the way he's been acting around you as well.
Yeah.
I know.
Like, he's literally, like, always there, like...
Well, that's that now.
I'm literally just going to be like...
You know what I mean?
Like, if he wants to be like that, like...
I just don't understand his, like...
..how his brain works.
Whatever happens, though, don't let Casey make you feel anything less.
Yeah.
Like, just remember, like...
You know what I mean?
I just think that's really...
I just think that's muggy as well.
Yeah.
Casey!
Where's that come from?
Oh, the balcony there.
Come up!
I've been summoned.
Please give him a good hold.
Please give him a cold stare on the stairs.
This is going to be like an awkward walk past.
Yeah.
You come down first.
No, but he's up there.
No, you come up.
What?
You go up.
Yeah, I was thinking you come down first.
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
What's up?
I've just heard, apparently,
you've been going to Callum, being like,
oh, yeah, I don't see a future with Eve.
I didn't say that.
That's a lie.
I just said...
What did you say, then?
Well, they just said, how's things been going with Eve?
And I said, yeah, really good.
Yeah.
Like, I'm just not sure if I see that spark yet.
Apparently, you said that you don't see a future with me.
I didn't say that.
Well, they said you did, but it's not like I'm sat here
thinking about, like, oh, yeah, like, the future,
about, like, oh, yeah, like, the future, like, me and you
going to get married and stuff.
I'm just enjoying my time here.
Yeah, and I've literally said that to them.
I feel like it's a bit muggy to be, like, like, imagine if I was
that old to the girls.
This has been taken way out of context.
No, no, no, but listen, I feel like you're just trying to, like,
put me down.
I think that's been taken way out of context.
I don't think it has, Casey.
I think it has.
It's come from something.
I'm just saying...
I was just being totally honest with them.
Yeah, OK.
It's not like I'm sat here...
It's really not, like, that deep.
Like, it's kind of deep to me, to be honest.
I feel like that just makes that...
Like, if I'm just being honest,
it just makes me want to fully retract.
OK, well, if you want to fully retract, that's fine.
I think instead of these villa whispers,
maybe you should have just gone straight up to Cal
and asked him what I said instead of...
No, I just wanted to come straight to you.
Yeah, but instead of Cal speaking to Sophie,
Sophie's speaking to you.
Should I ask Callum now, then?
Yeah, I'm happy for you two.
Callum?
Yeah?
Can you join us, please?
Oh!
Like...
Would you prefer me to go to Callum, or you?
I'm coming to you.
The boys have asked me how it's going,
and I've been very positive about it,
and I've said it's going really well,
but I just said I don't have that spark yet,
that's what I said.
I know what it is, Casey, I'm not stupid,
like now I just think.
But instead of these people saying this, saying that,
like it could have just been discussed between the two of us.
Hey, Callum, do you mind sitting down?
I'm sorry to drag you into this,
I just would like to clear things up.
I just feel like there's been whispers
going around the villa here,
and I don't think it's completely accurate, to be honest.
Okay, so did Casey say that he doesn't see a future with me?
No.
Well, that's what I heard.
Okay, well, you still said that it's not a spark.
No, I said the spark's not there yet.
Okay, I'm not having a go.
I'm trying to clarify what's been said.
So you don't think that we have a spark?
Did I say that?
I said it's not there yet.
It's not there yet?
Yeah, it's not there yet.
But that's not, doesn't mean it's not yet to come.
Sorry, Caleb, you don't have to be here now.
Sorry, I just didn't say the whole future thing and I'm glad you actually came.
I just said, yeah, just about on the outside, like...
Anyway, thank you.
Thanks.
Well, to be honest, Casey, I feel like that's, yeah, I've heard it now.
I'm sorry that we didn't have this conversation
with other people getting involved.
We don't have a spark, clearly.
So, from here, I feel like that's that.
I think I'm just not going to put effort into making something work,
but I just don't think we'll go anywhere.
OK.
Let's phone off.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to stay here and go get...
All right, OK.
..what's happening to me.
Girls! Hello?
Yeah?
Can you come back up?
Yeah.
OK.
Hey, girls.
What's up?
I don't see what happened.
Girls, I just kind of...
We knew you would, but what did he say?
What did he say?
He just said some stuff about, like,
oh, I like Eve and stuff, but I don't know about Sparks there yet.
Yeah.
I just don't like that vibe.
Yeah, exactly.
So he's just made me retreat.
I was like, I just think we should
just stop things here, then.
And what did he say?
He was just like, all right.
Oh
Can all Islanders gather around the fire pit immediately
It's not happy Texas it
Can you hear me?
The All-Stars have gathered to hear some big news.
All-Stars, step into the fire, deep into the fire, not around the fire, directly into the
fire.
Islanders, the public have been voting for
their favourite couple.
As Arabella and Adam are the newest couple, they are not included
than the vote.
The couples with the fewest votes
are at risk of being dumped from the island tonight.
In no particular order, the free couples with the fewest votes and therefore vulnerable
are...
Sophie and Josh.
Eve and Casey.
Until we find our breath
Georgia, I can tell you, bae.
Can all vulnerable couples please stand in front of the fire pit?
But one thing sure is true, I do not belong to you.
I do not belong to you.
The couple with the fewest votes and therefore dumped
from the island is.
Oh, God.
Eve and Kesa.
And I don't know anything, not anymore.
But one thing sure is true, I do not belong to you.
I do not belong to you.
****.
I love you, bro.
******* top gazer.
I'm so tired of running, I'm sick of letting you down.
I love you so much.
I don't want to say it's okay because you've gone saving.
Yeah.
I'm so tired of running, I'm sick of letting you down.
It's been a lonely road but it's all over now.
But everything happens for a reason, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It's just so hard because obviously we're like that.
I'm so tired of running, I'm sick of letting you down.
It's been a lonely road, but it's all over now.
But everything happens for a reason, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It's just so hard, because obviously, we're like that.
Like, we live together, we speak to each other every single day.
And I hear people talk about love just for something to say
Make sure you look after him now
Make sure you're with him if he looks a bit down
I think I'm just a bit good.
He hasn't actually met anyone
He deserves it like he's such a good lad
Yeah, that's never gonna show
Go on, quick!
It's just weird, like, when we won't be able to, like,
to know if each other are OK.
I feel like I've only just got Jess and Eve back, and, yeah,
just gutted, to be honest.
See you soon, OK?
You're going to be fine.
MUSIC PLAYS
From here on, cause you know that I know it's always been you
See you soon.
See you soon, brother.
From here on out
You arrived.
Hi.
Are you okay?
I mean, what can you do when the public say so?
Yeah, I'm good.
Today was a bit emotional for you, I feel like.
Yeah, I feel like if I think about my sister and Sophie,
I get upset, so I'm, like, thinking about them.
OK, just have a little moment.
Yeah.
I'll speak to Kasey first.
But, Kase, you...
What a journey you had!
A year later, back in the villa.
You had, obviously, a little bit of a moment with Georgia H.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you think that could have become something?
I think I'm a firm believer of if it didn't work out the first time,
it's not going to work out again, and I stand by that.
You were living your best life in there.
The twins came in and you were, like, love-struck eyes.
You had to chat with both of them,
got a kiss from both as well in the game.
How was that?
Yeah, it was great.
I mean, I can't complain.
Not many people can say they've kissed twins on the same night.
Yeah, no.
You and Jess obviously both liked Casey at the beginning
and you ended up with him.
And then, it just kind of stopped today.
I thought it was going well, and, like,
I really enjoy spending time with you,
but I just didn't have that spark yet, and that was it.
Yeah, and in hindsight, do you feel like
maybe you should have picked somebody else?
I'm still happy that I picked Casey,
because I feel like I can't see myself
with anyone else in there.
So, yeah, I don't regret anything,
but, yeah, I'm happy with how things have worked out, you know?
And obviously, you had to hear from Sophie.
how Casey felt.
How did that feel?
So I'm not, like, I'm not mad at you, like, going...
I feel like our conversation could be...
I don't know, I don't want you to think I'm mad
that you went to Callum or I found out from someone else.
I'm not even mad.
No, I think that was all explained.
Yeah, it was just having that conversation.
OK, yeah.
Like, it's fine.
It's not...
Like, that's not a thing to me, you know.
And are you hoping for your sister and Callum
to blossom and last forever?
How do you see that relationship?
You know what, I would have never expected it at all,
but I feel like they're really getting along.
Like, you can even see in there.
Yeah, definitely.
Like, they just talk and laugh, and I'm just like, wow.
Yeah.
Where did this come from?
Yeah, it surprised me, but I think they're actually
both really happy, like, in there together,
and happy for them.
All right, and what is next for you both?
Where are you off to now, then, Kase?
Back to square one, yeah.
Trying to find a girlfriend still.
Had Tom not been with Moni,
do you think something could have happened between you two?
Who knows?
All I know now is that I'm super happy for Molly and Tom.
Like, I'm rooting for them to win, so that's all that matters.
And how about you, Eve?
What's next?
I'm just going to wait for Jess to be with me.
Chill out.
Come, babe.
I know, yeah.
Just relax, wait for her to come back and then see where we go after that.
All right, well, it's been great to have you both back in the villa.
You may not have found love, but I hope you had the best time.
Thank you so much, guys.
Thank you.
We've got a text!
It's back.
Islanders, tonight you will get each other's pulses racing
in the All-Star Heart Rate Challenge.
SHE SCREAMS
Hashtag forbidden race on fire.
Hashtag don't skip a beat.
SHE SCREAMS
Yeah!
We've got a text!
It's back.
Yeah!